(Howard:)It's right there on the screen.
(Howard:)Austria does look like a wiener.
(Raj:)That's nothing, dude.
(Raj:)Go check out
how hung Florida is.
(laughing)
(Leonard:)I'm sure Mrs. Florida's
walking funny.
(Leonard:)Can we get back to work?
(Sheldon:)Yeah... he's right.
(Sheldon:)Oh, here's a thought.
(Sheldon:)What if we use some form of
operant conditioning techniques
(Sheldon:)to keep us from
getting off topic?
(Howard:)Like behavior modification?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, exactly.
(Sheldon:)Did you know
(Sheldon:)those techniques were used
to actually teach pigeons
(Sheldon:)to play ping-pong?
(Raj:)That cannot be true.
(ping-pong ball bouncing)
(Raj:)Hey, it was match point.
(Leonard:)Some psychologists
(Leonard:)perform operant conditioning
with punishment.
(Leonard:)Maybe we can come up
with a punishment
(Leonard:)for straying off topic.
(Raj:)Not getting to see who wins at
pigeon ping-pong comes to mind.